[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logos by nick.com and
这是尼克和Nick.com的徽标
in this tutorial i'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can create this
您可以如何创建此
shiny gold text using inkscape but
使用Inkscape的闪亮金色文本，但
before we get started if you'd like to
在我们开始之前，如果你愿意
learn everything that there is to know
学习一切该知道的东西
about inkscape
关于Inkscape
be sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos
视频
where i go over every tool and feature
在那里我检查了每一个工具和功能
in inkscape and i explain what it is and
在Inkscape中，我解释了它是什么
demonstrate how it works
演示其工作原理
i'll have a link in the description of
我会在描述中有一个链接
the video if you want to check that out
这个视频如果你想看看的话
so to get us started here in inkscape
为了让我们从Inkscape开始
let's first set up the document so that
让我们首先设置文档，以便
we all have a similar workflow
我们都有类似的工作流程
come up here to where it says view make
到这里来，上面写着要看风景
sure you have custom selected
确保您已自定义选择
and then come up to zoom and zoom in at
然后上前放大并放大
one to one
一对一
like that and then we want to make sure
像这样，然后我们想要确保
that we have snapping disabled for this
我们已为此禁用了快照
tutorial so up here at the very far top
教程就在最上面的最上面
left where it says enable snapping
留在显示启用捕捉的位置
go ahead and disable that and that will
继续禁用它，它就会
be good to get started so
很高兴能开始这样做
the first step is to create some text so
第一步是创建一些文本，以便
i'm going to grab the text tool right
我要抓起文本工具
here
这里
i'm going to click on the canvas to get
我要点击画布来获得
the blinking cursor and for this
闪烁的光标和这个
tutorial i will be using the word
教程我将使用这个词
gold text and i'm going to triple click
金色文本，我要点击三次
that to highlight all of it
为了突出这一切
and change the font so let's open up the
并更改字体，让我们打开
text editor up here and the font i'm
上面的文本编辑器和我使用的字体
going to be using for this tutorial is
本教程将使用的内容是
called
被呼叫
irs or ayers however it's pronounced i
IRS或Ayers，但发音为i
would recommend using this font if you'd
如果您愿意，我建议您使用此字体
like to make this
我想做这个
effect work because for whatever reason
效果起作用是因为无论出于什么原因
it just works really well with this font
它与这种字体配合使用时效果非常好
i've tried it with other fonts that
我已经用其他字体尝试过了
didn't quite
不是很清楚
look right but with this font it really
看起来是对的，但用这个字体真的
pops so i'll put a link in the
所以我会在
description to where you can download
可下载的位置的说明
this font for free
此字体免费
if you want to give that a try so go
如果你想试一试，那就去吧
ahead and click apply now
下一步，然后单击立即应用
and now i'm going to make this bigger so
现在我要把这件事做得更大
let me grab the select tool
让我拿一下选择工具
and i'm going to grab this arrow and
我要抓起这支箭
just scale this up i'm going to hold
把这个放大，我会拿着的
ctrl so it locks the proportions like
Ctrl键可锁定比例，如下所示
that
那
and now what i'm going to do is color
现在我要做的是上色
this in in order to make this look like
这样做是为了让这看起来像
gold i'm going to have to apply a
黄金，我将不得不申请一个
gradient
渐变
and the colors that i use in the
以及我在中使用的颜色
gradient are very important in fact
梯度实际上是非常重要的
they're so important that i've written
它们是如此重要，以至于我写下了
down the color codes for each individual
写下每个人的颜色代码
shade of the gradient
渐变阴影
and i will post them in the description
我会把它们贴在描述中
box of the video so that you can follow
盒子里的视频，这样你就可以跟着看了
along with what i'm doing exactly you
以及我正在做的事就是你
can go ahead and
可以继续下去，
copy and paste them yourself so let's
自己复制粘贴，这样我们就
apply a gradient here i'm going to grab
在这里应用渐变，我要抓住
the uh
那个呃
the edit objects colors gradients and
编辑对象颜色渐变和
stroke menu right here the fill and
笔划菜单就在这里，填充和
stroke menu
笔划菜单
you can click that button or press ctrl
您可以单击该按钮或按Ctrl键
shift and f to open that up
按Shift键和f键打开该窗口
and i'm going to come over here under
我将在下面来到这里
the fill tab
填充选项卡
i'm going to look for where it says
我要去找它上面写着
linear gradient right there and click on
线性渐变就在那里，然后单击
that
那
and then i'm going to grab the gradient
然后我要抓住渐变
tool and i'm going to click on this
工具，我要点击这个
little round stop right here
小圆车就停在这里
and i'm going to bring the opacity of
我要带来的是不透明的
that up so that right now it's a
所以现在它是一个
gradient going from black
渐变从黑色开始
to black so i will take this node right
设置为黑色，因此我将正确使用此节点
here and put this at the bottom of the
在这里，把这个放在
gradient
渐变
or the bottom of the text and i will
或者文本的底部，我会
take this node and put this at the top
把这个节点放在最上面
of the text and i will hold ctrl so that
我会按住Ctrl键，这样就可以
it's going up
它在上升
vertically just like that okay so right
垂直的就像那样，好的，所以对
now we have two different stops in this
现在我们有两个不同的停靠点
gradient
渐变
this gold color is going to have five
这个金色有五个
stops in it so i have to add
停在里面，所以我必须添加
three stops to this gradient so to do
此渐变的三个停靠点这样做
that i'm just going to double click on
我只需在上面双击
the line right here to add a new stop in
这条线在这里增加了一个新的停靠点
there
那里
i'll double click again to add another
我将再次双击以添加另一个
one and then one more
一次又一次
and now what i have to do is select each
现在我要做的就是选择每一个
of these stops and
在这些停靠站和
paste the color codes into them so i'll
将颜色代码粘贴到其中，这样我就可以
start at the top right here
从这里的顶部开始
working from top to bottom i'm gonna i
从上到下工作，我会
have a notepad opened on my other
在我的另一台电脑上打开记事本
monitor with these color codes written
写有这些颜色代码的显示器
out that i could just paste in there
我可以直接把它贴在里面
like i said i will have these in the
就像我说的，我会把这些放在
description box of the video so you can
视频的描述框，以便您可以
do the same you can just go ahead and
做同样的事情，你可以继续下去
copy and paste them right in
将它们复制并粘贴到
so i'm going to select each stop and
所以我要选择每一站
just paste them into the rgba box here
只需将它们粘贴到此处的RGBA框中
like that
就像这样
as you see me doing take this one as
就像你看到我做的那样，把这件事当作
well
井
paste that in there
把它贴在那里
this one here paste that in here
这一张贴在这张上
and then finally one more to go i'm just
最后再来一次，我只是
ctrl c to copy
要复制的Ctrl c
ctrl v to paste just like that
按Ctrl v键即可粘贴
and now i want to adjust the positions
现在我想调整位置
of these colors on the gradient i want
在我想要的渐变颜色中
to take this top one and move this a
把上面这一张，把这张
little closer to the top like that
像这样离顶端近一点
and i want to take this one right here
我想把这个放在这里
this middle one which is like the dark
中间这个就像黑暗一样
the darker shade and bring that towards
较暗的色调，并将其带到
the top third or the bottom of the top
顶部的三分之一或顶部的底部
third of the text right there right
文本的第三部分就在那里
about there looks pretty good
在那里看起来很不错
and then take this one right here and
然后把这个放在这里，然后
bring this up closer towards that darker
把这个拿近一点，靠近那个更暗的
one like that
像这样的
and that right there is the look we're
而这就是我们的眼神
going for this is starting uh starting
去做这个是开始，呃开始
to come together it's starting to look
为了走到一起，它开始看起来
like gold text
点赞金色文本
only now we're going to add a little bit
只是现在我们要添加一点
of depth to it so let's grab the select
所以让我们抓住精选
tool
工具
and let's create a duplicate copy of
让我们创建一个副本
this text let's right click this and go
此文本让我们右键单击此文本，然后开始
to duplicate
复制
and let's give this a outline otherwise
另外，让我们给出一个提纲
known as a stroke i'm going to i'm just
就像我要去的中风，我只是
going to use the color red for now i'm
现在我要用红色，我是
going to hold
我要等一下
shift and click on the color red to give
按住Shift键并单击要显示的红色
that an outline like that
像这样的提纲
and then i'm going to send that to the
然后我会把它发送给
back i'm going to come up here to this
回到这里，我要到这里来
button that says
按钮上写着
lower selection to the bottom click on
将所选内容降低到底部，然后单击
that so that it goes behind the original
这样它就会落后于原来的
text
文本
and i'll come over here to the stroke
我会走到这里来看比赛
style tab and i want to increase the
Style选项卡，我想增加
size of this stroke
此笔划的大小
maybe not that much let me change this
也许没那么多，让我换一下吧
to pixels let's try something like
到像素，让我们尝试一下，比如
six or maybe five
六个，也许五个
maybe not that much i want i don't want
也许没有我想要的那么多，我不想要
this to be too thick maybe it's four and
这个不会太厚，可能是四个
a half that should be pretty good
一半应该是相当不错的
okay that looks good enough right there
好的，就在那里看起来足够好了
somewhere there about it doesn't have to
在那里的某个地方，它不需要
be exactly the same size as mine so just
和我的尺寸一模一样，所以
go ahead and eyeball it
向前看吧，看着它
and now i want to give that red outline
现在我想给出那个红色的轮廓
the same gradient
相同的坡度
that the gold text has only in reverse
黄金文本只有相反的
so let's come over here to the stroke
所以让我们到这里来看看划水
paint tab
绘制选项卡
and click on linear gradient and we're
然后点击线性渐变，我们就会
going to choose our gradient from our
我们将从我们的
list over here
名单在这里
and now let's grab the gradient tool so
现在让我们抓住渐变工具
we can adjust the position of that
我们可以调整它的位置
gradient
渐变
so right here on the vertical axis you
所以就在这里的垂直轴上
can see our original gradient
可以看到我们原始的渐变
over here on the horizontal axis that's
在这里的水平轴上，这是
the current gradient for the stroke
笔划的当前渐变
so what i want to do is do the same
所以我想做的就是做同样的事情
thing with the original gradient only in
仅具有原始渐变的对象
reverse if you see here
如果你看到这里，就可以倒车了
on the original gradient we have the
在原始渐变上，我们有
circle node on top
顶部的圆形节点
and the square node on the bottom i want
底部的正方形节点我想要
to do the opposite for this one i want
对我想要的这件事做相反的事情
to put the circle node on the bottom
将圆形节点放在底部
oops didn't mean to do that put the
哎呀，我不是故意要这么做的
circle node on the bottom
底部的圆形节点
and put the square note on the top and
把正方形音符放在上面，然后
again again just hold ctrl to lock it
同样，只需按住Ctrl键即可锁定它
onto the
放到了
vertical axis like that and there you go
像这样的垂直轴，你就可以了
so let's grab the select tool now
现在，让我们抓起选择工具
click off of that to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
it's starting to come together now what
它现在开始走到一起了什么
i'm going to do is i'm going to break
我要做的是我要打破
these letters apart and adjust the
将这些字母分开并调整
spacing between them so
它们之间的间距是这样的
let's click and drag over both of these
让我们在这两个上面单击并拖动
text objects and go to path
文本对象和转到路径
object to path and then ungroup over
对象添加到路径，然后取消分组
here where it says ungroup selected
此处显示取消分组所选内容
groups
群组
and now it's individual letters like
现在它是像这样的单个字母
that so i'm going to click and drag over
所以我要点击并拖动到
this letter g
这个字母g
i'm going to zoom in on this a little
我要把这个放大一点
bit i'm going to hold ctrl and roll up
我要按住Ctrl键，然后卷起来
the mouse wheel a couple of times to
鼠标滚来滚去几次
zoom in
放大
and i'm just going to hold ctrl i'm
我要按住Ctrl键我要
going to click and drag over this letter
要在这封信上单击并拖动
g right here so i have both objects
就在这里，所以我有两个物体
selected
已选择
and i'm going to hold ctrl and just move
我要按住Ctrl键，然后移动
this over like that i'm just manually
就这样结束了，我只是手动的
adjusting the spacing between these
调整它们之间的间距
letters here as you can see
如你所见，这里有字母
clicking and dragging over all three
在所有三个位置上单击并拖动
letters
书信
moving it in then i'm going to click and
把它移进去，然后我要点击并
drag over the whole word move that in
拖过整个单词将其移入
and again while we're doing this we're
当我们这样做的时候，我们又一次
holding ctrl on the keyboard so that it
按住键盘上的Ctrl键，以便它
locks it onto the vertical axis like
将其锁定在垂直轴上，就像
that
那
okay that looks pretty good move this in
好的，看起来很不错，把这个搬进来
and then finally this one this one's a
最后这一张这张是
little too close to the t so i'm going
离T太近了，所以我要走了
to move that back just a tiny bit
把它稍稍往后移一点
and maybe i'll put some more space
也许我会放更多的空间
between the two words like that
在这样的两个字之间
that right there looks good so we'll
就在那里看起来很好，所以我们
click off of that to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
now what i want to do is unify
现在我想要做的是统一
these letters together these these uh
这些字母加在一起这些这些
the letters on top anyway
不管怎样，上面的字母
so i'm going to click on the letter g
所以我要点击字母g
and then i'm going to hold shift and
然后我要按住班次
click on all of the other letters
点击所有其他字母
so that we have all of them selected and
所以我们把它们都选好了，
unify them together by going to path
通过转到Path将它们统一在一起
union and the reason why i do that is
联合，我这么做的原因是
because now i want to create
因为现在我想要创造
sort of like a reflective light or like
有点像反射光或类似的东西
a shine coming off of the top of this
一道亮光从这上面闪耀出来
text here and i'm going to need a
在这里发短信，我需要一个
duplicate copy of that text to do that
要做到这一点，请复制文本副本
so
所以
with the text selected right click it
选择文本后，右键单击它
and go to duplicate
并转到复制
and make the duplicate copy white and
并将副本设置为白色和
now we're going to create a little bit
现在我们要创建一点
of an offset
偏移量的
of this white text right here so let's
就在这里，所以让我们
come over here to the
到这里来，到
path effects menu we'll go to path and
路径效果菜单，我们将转到路径和
click on path effects
单击路径效果
and i'm going to click the plus icon
我要点击加号图标
here to add a new path effect
在此添加新的路径效果
and the path effect we're looking for is
我们正在寻找的路径效应是
offset which is right here
偏移量就在这里
and with offset enabled i'm going to
启用偏移后，我将执行以下操作
zoom in a little bit what i want to do
稍微放大我想要做的事情
is grab the edit paths by nodes tool
是抓取按结点编辑路径工具
which is right here
它就在这里
and what you should be looking for is
你应该寻找的是
this little circle node right here if
如果这里的这个小圆圈节点
you notice everything else is a square
你会注意到其他东西都是正方形
node we're looking for this circle node
节点我们正在寻找这个圆形节点
right here let me zoom in on that a
就在这里，让我放大这个a
little bit
一点点
and i'm going to take this circle node
我要把这个圆圈节点
and just click and drag that down a
只需点击并将其拖到下一个
little bit just to
一点点只是为了
give that a little bit of an offset and
给它一点补偿，然后
what you notice what it's doing here is
你注意到它在这里做的是
it's shaving off a little space
它正在削减一小块空间
off of around the edges of the letters
在字母的边缘周围
like that which is exactly what we're
就像这样，这就是我们
looking for
寻找
okay so i'm happy with how that looks
好的，我对它的样子很满意
i'm going to finalize it by going to
我将通过以下方式来完成它：
path
路径
path object to path grab the select tool
路径对象到路径抓取选择工具
i'm going to press 1 on the keyboard to
我要按键盘上的1键来
zoom back out to a hundred percent
缩小到100%
and let's close out of the path effects
让我们来结束路径效果
menu we don't need that anymore
菜单我们不再需要它了
now what i'm gonna do is i'm going to
现在我要做的是我要
create an ellipse going over the top
创建一个越过顶部的椭圆
half of this white text here so let me
这里有一半的白色文字，所以让我
grab these circles and ellipses tool
抓取这些圆和椭圆工具
i'll click and drag to create an ellipse
我将单击并拖动以创建一个椭圆
going over the top of it like that
像那样做得太过火了
and i want to get rid of that outline
我想摆脱那个提纲
let's hold shift and click the little
让我们按住Shift键并单击小
red x down here to get rid of that
红x来这里把它处理掉
outline
大纲
and i'm just going to make this a
我只想让这件事成为
contrasting color for now maybe
目前可能会形成对比的颜色
something like green
类似于绿色的东西
bring the opacity down so i can see
把不透明度调低，这样我就能看到了
where it lines up with the rest of the
在那里它与其余的
text
文本
and let me grab the select tool right
让我来拿一下选择工具
here now if you notice the bottom edge
现在如果你注意到底部的边缘
of this green ellipse
这个绿色椭圆形的
i'm paying attention to where it lines
我在注意它的线在哪里
up with the text i want it above this
在文本上，我想要它在这个上面
part of the g
G的一部分
but below this part of the g right here
但在G的这一部分下面就在这里
right about here we want this to be in
就在这里，我们想把这个放在
about the top third of the text as you
大约是文本的前三分之一，因为你
see here i like this position
看这里，我喜欢这个位置
so i'm going to leave that as it is i'm
所以我要让它保持原样我是
going to hold shift click the white text
按住Shift键单击白色文本
so that we have the green ellipse and
这样我们就有了绿色的椭圆
the white text selected at the same time
同时选择的白色文本
and go to path intersection
然后走到小路交叉口
and what we have to do now is give this
我们现在要做的就是把这个
thing a gradient so let's come over here
渐变，所以我们到这边来
to the fill
满载而归
tab and click on the linear gradient
选项卡，然后单击线性渐变
button
按钮
and then grab the gradient tool over
然后抓住渐变工具
here and take this
给你，拿着这个
little uh white stop over here and put
小，呃，怀特，停在这里，把
this towards the bottom of that white
这个接近白色的底部
object
对象
and then take this circle stop and put
然后把这个圆圈停下来，放在
this towards the top i'm going to hold
这个朝向顶端，我要拿着
ctrl
Ctrl键
to lock it onto the vertical axis like
将其锁定到垂直轴上，如下所示
that now if you notice i'm not putting
现在如果你注意到我没有把
this
这
exactly at the bottom of the white text
恰好在白文的底部
there i'm putting it slightly below so
我把它放在稍微下面一点，所以
it's not so
事情不是这样的
it's not so harsh and this one right
它不是那么刺耳，这一次是对的
here this is not going all the way up to
在这里，这并不是一直到
the top i'm putting this down to about
我把这件事归结为大约
here like that
在这里就像这样
and at this point you may have to adjust
在这一点上，你可能不得不调整
the position of the original gradient so
原始渐变的位置因此
let me click on the gold text
让我点击金色文本
and i'm going to take this if you notice
如果你注意到的话我要拿着这个
i'm going to take this stop right here
我要在这里停一下。
and bring that down a little bit
把它降下来一点
and bring this down a little bit as well
把这个也降下来一点
maybe bring this down to here
也许把这个带到这里来
whoops messed up there if you mess up
哦，如果你搞砸了，那就糟了
and do something like this just hit ctrl
然后按下Ctrl键就可以做这样的事情
z on the keyboard to undo what you just
键盘上的Z键来撤消您刚才所做的操作
did
做
okay that's looking that's looking
好的，就是这样，就是这样
pretty good right there okay so let me
很好，好的，让我来
grab the select tool
抓起选择工具
click off of it to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
and the final step would be to add a
最后一步是添加一个
little bit of a drop shadow to this to
这是一个小小的阴影
make it pop a little more so to do that
让它更流行一点，这样做
i'm going to click on the gold text i'm
我要点击黄金文本I‘m
going to duplicate it by pressing ctrl d
按Ctrl d复制它
on the keyboard and i'm going to make
在键盘上，我要制作
that black and i'm going to bring this
那个黑色的，我要带上这个
down
降下来
slightly down i'm going to bring it down
稍微往下一点，我要把它降下来
slightly
略微
and to the right slightly and i'm gonna
稍微向右一点，我就会
lower that to the bottom with this
用这个把它降到最低
button over here that says lower
这里的按钮，上面写着更低
selection to the bottom
选择到底部
maybe even use the arrow keys to adjust
甚至可以使用箭头键进行调整
it a little bit that right there is
它有一点就在那里
pretty good
挺不错的
and i will give this a little bit of a
我会给这一点一点
blur
模糊
just like that and then finally bring
就这样，然后终于带来了
the opacity down a little bit
不透明度降低了一点
maybe reduce the blur reduce the opacity
也许可以减少模糊，减少不透明度
and you get the idea you just play with
你就会明白你只是在玩弄
a little bit and as you can see we've
一点，如你所见，我们已经
finished creating our gold text now one
已完成创建我们的黄金文本，现在为
final thing i would i would recommend
我推荐的最后一件事
using this for a dark background for
使用此选项作为黑色背景
whatever reason this
不管是什么原因
gold text effect really pops better on
金色文本效果真的更好地弹出
dark backgrounds so
背景很暗，所以
let me create a rectangle going over
让我创建一个经过的矩形
this whole thing like this
这整件事就像这样
let me bring the opacity of that all the
让我把这一切的不透明带到
way up grab the select tool
向上，抓起选择工具
lower that to the bottom and maybe make
把它降到最低，也许会
this like a lighter shade of gray over
这就像是浅灰色的覆盖
here where it says fill
在这里它写着填满
i'm going to select hsl and i'm gonna
我要选择HSL，我要
look at this l row like this and just
看着L这一排，就像这样
bring that down a little bit
把那个放低一点
and then hold shift and click on the
然后按住Shift键并单击
text and uh center it up
文本，并将其居中
using the alignment menu so i'm gonna
使用对齐菜单，所以我要
open up the align and distribute menu
打开对齐并分布菜单
over here and set this the relative to
在这里，将此相对设置为
set it to last selected center it on the
将其设置为最后一次选择，并将其置于
vertical and horizontal axis like that
像这样的垂直轴和水平轴
and you may want to adjust the drop
你可能会想要调整下落
shadow drop shadow a little bit so let
阴影投下阴影一点，所以让
me zoom in a little more
我再放大一点
let me just bring this out
让我把这句话说出来
let me go back to the fill and stroke
让我回到填充物和划水
menu maybe give this
菜单可能会给你这个
bring the opacity of it up now since
现在就把它的不透明带上来，因为
it's on a darker background
它的背景比较暗
maybe make that a little darker and i
也许让它变得更黑暗一点，然后我
think i will call it a day right there
我想今天就到此为止吧
so that should do it for this tutorial
对于本教程来说，应该就是这样了
that is how you can go about creating
这就是你可以开始创作的方式
that gold text
那个金色的文字
using inkscape so if you have any
使用Inkscape，所以如果您有
questions just leave a comment below and
问题只需在下面留下评论和
as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]